dragdis.com 2015-09-19

# Privacy policy | Dragdis

January 31, 2014 

These terms provide privacy rules applicable to all information collected, submitted or processed when you access, install or use the Dragdis Services. By accessing or using the Dragdis Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and by our Terms of Service. All definitions used and referred in this Privacy Policy are the same as in our Terms of Service. 

**How do we collect information?**

We collect information in two ways: 

1\. When you give it to us or give us permission to obtain it.When you sign up for or use the Dragdis Services (create Dragdis account), you voluntarily give us certain information. This may include your name, email address that you used to sign up, and any other information you provide us. 

You also may give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link your Facebook or Twitter account to Dragdis Services, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts. The information we obtain from those services depends on your settings or their privacy policies. 

If you choose to share any content saved and retained with the Dragdis Services with another person, you will need to provide to us a valid email address for that person. You also need to provide your username and password for third party websites in order to access the content published on such sites. We also collect information if you contact us for support or help, submit an application or otherwise communicate with us. 

The information which you supply to us enables us to customize and enhance the services we provide to you. In addition, it helps us communicate with you about our news, events, promotions and new products and services. 

2\. When you use the Dragdis Services.In most cases, every time you use a website, mobile application, or other Internet service, there's certain information that gets created and recorded in an automated way. The same is true when you use Dragdis Services. 

When you use Dragdis Services, our servers may automatically record information about your interaction with the Dragdis Services ("log data"), including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This log data may include without limitation your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web page you were visiting before you came to Dragdis Services, your browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, and how you used Dragdis Services. 

Depending on how you're accessing the Dragdis Services, we may use "cookies" (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our website, unique to your Dragdis Services account or your browser), or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies, we may use "session" cookies (that last until you close your browser) or "persistent" cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). For example, we may use cookies to store your language preferences or other Dragdis Services settings so you don't have to set them up every time you access Dragdis Services. You may decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features, you may be required to enter your password more frequently during a session, and you may be unable to install or use certain Dragdis Services. 

In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device that you're using to access Dragdis Services, including what type of device it is, what operating system you're using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you're using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you're using a Mac or a PC, or an iPad or a Surface. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider. 

We always use non-identifying, aggregated information to analyze the manner in which the Dragdis Services are used. We collect information about the URLs, titles and content of the websites and other information you save and retain with the Dragdis Services, such as information related to the manner in which you access the Dragdis Services, metadata concerning User Content, and other interactions with the Dragdis Services. We also collect information about your use of the Dragdis Services, such as what you have read or viewed, which device you used to have accessed such content, what you choose to save and retain, what you choose remove, and what you choose to share with others. We compile aggregated data by combining information from many users, without including any information that could be used to identify you or anyone else by name. 

**How do we use the information we collect?**

We use the information we collect to operate and provide Dragdis Services to you,to improve them and make them better, to develop new products, to protect Dragdis and our users, to administer your use of the Dragdis Services, to better understand your needs and interests, to personalize and improve your experience, and to deliver the other products and services we offer. For example, we may log how often people use two different versions of the Dragdis Services, which can help us understand which version is better. 

We also use the information we collect to send you updates, newsletters, marketing materials and other information that may be of interest to you. For example, depending on your email notification settings, we may send you weekly updates that include items that you may like or find interesting. You can decide to stop getting these updates by updating your account settings (or through other settings we may provide). However, you may not disable essential system messages, because we may need to inform you of very important things related to Dragdis or to your account. 

We also share aggregated data and related usage information with third parties, including content providers, website operators, advertisers and publishers, but this aggregate information does not contain any personal information which can identify you or any other individual user. The sharing of aggregated data may include reports provided to third parties based on the information we collect and analyze. We do not control how third parties disclose or use the information we share with them. 

The information we collect may be "personally identifiable" (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or "non-personally identifiable" (meaning it can't be used to specifically identify you). We use both types of information, and combinations of both types, as described above. We do not share any personally identifiable information with any third-party. We may use or store information wherever Dragdis does business, including countries outside your own. 

We may employ third party companies or individuals to process personal information on our behalf based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy. For example, we may share data with a security consultant to help us get better at identifying spam or with our accountants to make sure we’re keeping the books correctly. In addition, some of the information we request may be collected by third party providers on our behalf. 

If we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety, rights, or property of the public, any person, or Dragdis; or to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 

We may engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy. 

**What choices do I have about my information?**

Our goal is to give you simple and meaningful choices over your information. If you have a Dragdis Services account, many of the choices you have on Dragdis Services are built directly in to the Dragdis Services or your account settings. For example, you can: 

Link or unlink your Dragdis Services account from an account on another service (e.g., Facebook or Twitter). For some services (like Facebook), you can also choose whether or not to publish your activity on Dragdis Services to that service. 

Close your account at any time. When you close your account, we'll deactivate it and remove your User Content from Dragdis Services. We may retain archived copies of your information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes (including to help address criminal activity, fraud and spam). 

You may have choices available to you through the device or software you use to access Dragdis Services. For example, the browser you use may provide you with the ability to control cookies or other types of local data storage. 

**How do we make changes to this policy?**

We may change this policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. For your convenience, we include the effective date of the Privacy Policy at the beginning of this document, so that you can easily ascertain whether it has been updated since the last time you viewed the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Dragdis Services constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy at the time of each use. If you continue to use Dragdis Services after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or obtain your consent as required by law. If you have questions about any of the provisions described above, please contact us. 

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Dragdis, LLC  
+1 415 992 5347  
hello@dragdis.com  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
